http://www.outdoorsinc.com/pages/privacy-policy

Free SmartPost Shipping on All Orders Over $50!
Search
Free SmartPost Shipping on All Orders Over $50!
Privacy / Security Policy
Your Privacy:
Information You Provide: You provide certain
personally identifiable information (such as your name, email
address and credit card information) to OutdoorsInc.com when choosing to make purchases or participate in various
activities on the Site such as posting messages in our forums, sending
feedback, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other
email updates.
Other Information We Track: This Site uses
passive tracking technologies to log non-identifiable information such
as IP address, browser type and Site usage (for example: what pages are
accessed, how often, referring/exit pages and URLs). We may also employ
"cookies" or similar technologies that provide additional functionality
to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. You can set
your browser to reject cookies, but if you do, some features on our Site
will not function normally.
How We Use This Information: We use the information we collect to respond to your requests and
provide better customer service, process payments, let you know
about new offerings and other news from OutdoorsInc.com, ask
for your input and feedback on what we are doing, provide personalized
services and recommendations, and as may otherwise be described in this
Privacy Policy or at the time that we collect information from you.
We use both your personally identifiable information and certain
non-personally identifiable site usage data to improve your shopping experience with OutdoorsInc.com. We may also use this information to improve the quality and
design of the Site, create new features, promotions, and services
by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends.
Bottom Line: Your privacy is important to us. OutdoorsInc.com is extremely diligent in keeping your information safe and
secure. Our privacy statement guarantees specifically that we will NOT
share, barter, sell, or trade your confidential information with ANYONE,
under ANY circumstances without your prior consent.
Your Security:
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you
enter sensitive information, such as a credit card number, we encrypt
that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). You will
see an icon, resembling a padlock, displayed at the bottom right-hand
side of most browser windows during SSL transactions
that involve credit cards and other forms of payment. This icon
indicates the information entered into the page is 128-bit SSL
encrypted. We follow
generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal
information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we
receive it. OutdoorsInc.com ensures that your information and your order
data is
hidden from prying eyes both during and after transactions. If you have
any
questions about security on OutdoorsInc.com, please email us at
customerservice@outdoorsinc.com.
